Deep Kidiya Front End Developer

- +91 8320256818
- ⋈ kidiyadeep@gmail.com
- ★ bit.ly/deepkidiya

Profile

Creative Front-End Developer with 1.5+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing and developing web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Seeking for new opportunities and challenges that will expand my skill set.

Professional Experience

11/2021 – present HTML CSS Developer

Inclusive Studio

- Translated necessary requirements into HTML code.
- Created visual media for online campaigns.
- Managed to simultaneously work on multiple projects without deviation.

09/2020 – 10/2021 Web Designer

Classy Touch Pvt. Ltd.

- Designed an ecommerce website for classtouch.in
- Designed custom graphics and banners for website, social media, etc.
- Handled all composition, color, illustration, typography, and branding for client projects

Education

 $07/2019 - 07/2020 \qquad \textbf{ITI in Multimedia Graphics}$

ITI Anjar Polytechnic

Skills

HTML5	• • • •	CSS3	• • • • •
JavaScript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$	Bootstrap5	• • • • •
React.js	• • • • •	CorelDraw	• • • • •
Adobe Xd	• • • • •	Figma	• • • • •

- Gaming - Travelling

- Music

Languages

English